<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COMP3606_ASG2</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_explore_screen">ExploreScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_android">AboutAndroid</string>
    <string name="title_activity_android_guicomponents">AndroidGUIComponents</string>

    <string name="What_is_Android">
        Android is an operating system and programming platform by Google for smartphones and other mobile devices (such as tablets).
        It can run on many different devices from many different manufacturers. Android includes a software development kit for writing original code and assembling software modules to create apps for Android users. It also provides a marketplace to distribute apps.  All together Android represents an ecosystem for mobile apps. Android is developed by the Open Handset Alliance, which is led by Google. Some of the well-known Android device manufacturers include Acer, HTC, Samsung, LG, Sony Ericsson and Motorola.
    </string>

    <string name="Toast_faqs">
        A toast provides simple feedback about an operation in a small popup. It only fills the amount of space required for the message and the current activity remains visible and interactive. Toasts automatically disappear after a timeout.
    </string>

    <string name="Spinner_faqs">
        Spinners provide a quick way to select one value from a set. In the default state, a spinner shows its currently selected value. Touching the spinner displays a dropdown menu with all other available values, from which the user can select a new one.
    </string>

    <string name="Button_faqs">
        A button consists of text or an icon (or both text and an icon) that communicates what action occurs when the user touches it.
    </string>

    <string name="ImageView_faqs">
        Displays image resources, for example android.graphics.Bitmap or android.graphics.drawable.Drawable resources. ImageView is also commonly used to apply tints to an image and handle image scaling.
    </string>

    <string name="ListView_faqs">
        Displays a vertically-scrollable collection of views, where each view is positioned immediately below the previous view in the list. For a more modern, flexible, and performant approach to displaying lists, use RecyclerView.
    </string>

    <string name="EditText_faqs">
        A user interface element for entering and modifying text.
    </string>

    <string name="DatePicker_faqs">
        Provides a widget for selecting a date.
    </string>

    <string name="NumberPicker_faqs">
        A widget that enables the user to select a number from a predefined range. There are two flavors of this widget and which one is presented to the user depends on the current theme.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_quiz_screen">QuizScreen</string>

    <!--Quiz Questions -->

    <string name="question1">  <!--EditText-->
        1. What is a user interface element in android for entering and modifying text?
    </string>

    <string name="question2"> <!--Button-->
        2. A ______________ consists of text or an icon (or both text and an icon) that communicates what action occurs when the user touches it.
    </string>

    <string name="question3"> <!--Toast-->
        3. What provides a simple feedback about an operation in a small popup?
    </string>

    <string name="question4"> <!--Spinner-->
        4. What provides a quick way to select one value from a set?
    </string>

    <string name="question5"> <!--DatePicker-->
        5. __________ provides a widget for selecting a date.
    </string>
</resources>
